{
  "sentences": [
    {
      "question": "Мне нужно улучшить свои навыки разговорной речи и аудирования на английском языке.",
      "answer": "I need to improve my speaking and listening skills in English",
      "tasks": ["need", "to", "improve"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Я надеюсь не потерять свой багаж в аэропорту",
      "answer": "I hope not to lose my luggage in an airport",
      "tasks": ["hope", "not", "to", "lose"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Трудно говорить с новыми людьми",
      "answer": "It's hard to speak with new people",
      "tasks": ["hard", "to", "speak"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Важно не попасть в аварию",
      "answer": "It's important not to have an accident",
      "tasks": ["important", "not", "to", "have"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Я не знаю, как улучшить свои знания английского языка",
      "answer": "I don't know how to improve my English skills",
      "tasks": ["how", "to", "improve"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Она разослала много приглашений на вечеринку, но не знает, кто их пример",
      "answer": "She sent a lot of invitations to the party, but she doesn't know who to accept them",
      "tasks": ["know", "to", "accept"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Я ем здоровую пищу, чтобы похудеть",
      "answer": "I eat healthy food to reduce my weight",
      "tasks": ["to", "reduce"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Я просыпаюсь рано, чтобы успеть сделать много полезных дел",
      "answer": "I wake up early to have time to do many useful things",
      "tasks": ["to", "have", "time", "to", "do"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Покупка новой одежды делает мою жену счастливее",
      "answer": "Buying new clothes makes my wife happier",
      "tasks": ["Buying"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Mы рассматриваем возможность присутствия на встрече",
      "answer": "We are considering the possibility of attending the meeting",
      "tasks": ["attending"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Мне нравится расслабляться и слушать музыку после тяжелой работы",
      "answer": "I like relaxing and listening to music after hard work",
      "tasks": ["relaxing", "listening"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Он лег спать не поужинав",
      "answer": "He went to bed without having supper",
      "tasks": ["having"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Я сожалею, что не учил английский в школе",
      "answer": "I regret not learning English at school",
      "tasks": ["learning"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Мне не хочется просыпаться слишком рано",
      "answer": "I don't feel like waking up too early ",
      "tasks": ["waking"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Я думаю сменить работу",
      "answer": "I'm thinking of changing my work",
      "tasks": ["changing"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Она не против путешествовать со мной",
      "answer": "She don't mind travelling with me",
      "tasks": ["travelling"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Я не хочу целый год жить в Армении.",
      "answer": "I don't want to go on living in Armenia whole year",
      "tasks": ["living"]
    }
  ],
  "grammar": {
    "src": ["./grammar/to-&-gerund.webp", "./grammar/verbs+infinitive.webp", "./grammar/verbs+ing.webp"],
    "layout": ""
  }
}
